A Finding Aid to the Alexander Archipenko Papers, 1904-1986, bulk 1930-1964, in the Archives of American Art AAA.archalex
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Material, 1904-1964; Series 10; 3.6 Linear feet Boxes 14-15, 17-21, 26-27
  - Negatives, circa 1920-1960; 10.9
    - Film Negatives, 10.9.1
      - Miscellaneous Subjects (Box 18)
        - Book Cover, Archipenko: Fifty Creative Years, 1908-1958, circa 1960 (Box 18, Folder 21)
        - Broadside, "50th Archipenko Exhibition in the United States,", 1944 (Box 18, Folder 22)
        - Cartoon, "Au Salon des Independents [1912],", circa 1940-1960 (Box 18, Folder 23)
        - Cat, circa 1940-1960 (Box 18, Folder 24)
        - Lecture Illustration Depicting Various Concave Forms, circa 1940-1960 (Box 18, Folder 25)
        - Legal Document Concerning Residence in France [1916], circa 1940-1960 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Illustrations for Archipenko: Fifty Creative Years, 1908-195 8, circa 1960 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Glass Negatives, 10.9.2
      Miscellaneous subjects include caricatures of Archipenko and his art, articles, a poem, and a cover of an exhibition catalog.
      - Miscellaneous Subjects, 1910-1940; 15 Glass negatives (Box 20)
      - Works of Art by Alexander Archipenko, Prints, Drawings, Paintings, and Sculptures, 1910-1940; 58 Glass negatives (Box 20-21)
      - Works of Art by Angela Archipenko, Sculpture, 1910-1940; 1 Glass negatives (Box 21)